beefree.io 2019-12-14

# Privacy Policy - BEE free

Effective Date: July 31, 2018

## (1) Introduction

We at MailUp Inc., an email marketing company (“ **MailUp** ” or “ **we** ”), respect your concerns about privacy.

This policy describes the types of information we collect from you when you visit **<https://beefree.io/>** (including any third-level-domain and sub-domains) (“ **Website** ”) and when you use our Services, how we use the information, with whom we share it and the choices available to users of our Website and Services regarding our use of the information. We also describe our practices for protecting that information and how you can contact us about our privacy practices.

If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website or Services. **_By accessing or using this Website, or any of the Services it provides, you agree to this Privacy Policy._**  This policy may change from time to time (see _Changes to our Privacy Policy_ ). Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

This online Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our Website and Services and not to information collected offline.

Our Website allows you to access the following services (“ **Services** ”):

  * An online email editor named “BEE Free” that enables users to create responsive email using a drag-&-drop user interface (“ **BEE Free** ”);
  * A JavaScript web plugin named “BEE Plugin” that is a web plugin, easily embeddable in other software applications, and used for the purpose to allow users of those applications to create email messages using a drag-&-drop user interface (“ **BEE Plugin** ”);
  * An online email editor named “BEE Pro”, that enables users to create, save and edit an email message using a drag-&-drop user interface (“ **BEE Pro** ”);
  * An online community that users can use to ask and find information about our Services (“ **Community** ”).
  * A newsletter to get regular updates from us (“ **Newsletter** ”).

## (2) Information we collect about you and how we collect it

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, and telephone numbers; and about your Internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.

We collect this information directly from you when you provide it to us, or automatically as you navigate through the Website. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies.

In connection with the provision of the Services, MailUp collects and stores the following information (“ **Information** ”):

  * **Anonymous information** from visitors to these Website. We use this information to run our Website more effectively and improve it over time. For example, we may detect the type of browser you are using and use that information to redirect you to a section of the Website that works best for your browser, and use the same information to increase browser compatibility over time. Similarly, we may attempt to detect your geolocation and direct you to a version of the Website that is written in a language that might better match your needs. We reserve the right to maintain, use, and share Anonymous Information without limitation.
  * **Personal Information related to the use of BEE Plugin and BEE Pro** (e-mail address and password) from users that elect to use BEE Plugin or BEE Pro. We use this information in order to communicate with you and fulfill our contractual obligations.
  * **Billing Information related to the use of BEE Plugin** **and BEE Pro** (name, surname, company name, tax ID, address) from users that activate a BEE Plugin or BEE Pro subscription. We do not and will not collect and store your credit card number, which is handled as indicated in section 8,  _Credit card number and billing information_.
  * **Personal Information related to the use of BEE Free and BEE Pro** (e-mail address of the recipient and email content) from users that elect to use the ‘Send test’ feature in BEE Free or BEE Pro. We may process and store for statistical, legal and quality analysis all data deriving from the use of BEE Free or BEE Pro. We may use and diffuse, only in aggregate form, the results of these analyses. As owner of these aggregated data, we will take care to assure the full anonymization of the analysed data to avoid any processing and diffusion or communication.
  * **Personal Information related to the use of our Newsletters  **(e-mail address), from users that request information about our Services. We use this information in order to communicate with you.

## (3) How we use your information

We use Information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us;
  * To process your payments and to create and manage your account;
  * To send you our newsletter, unless you opted out;
  * To respond to your inquiries;
  * To perform data analysis (including anonymization and aggregation of personal information);
  * To operate, evaluate and improve our business (including developing new products and services; enhancing and improving our products and services; managing our communications; analysing our products and customer base; performing data analytics; and performing accounting and other internal functions);
  * To protect against, identify and prevent fraud and other unlawful activities, claims or liabilities;
  * To comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards and our policies.

## (4) How we disclose your Information

We never use or share Personal Information in ways unrelated to the ones described in this Privacy Policy, and we will not do so in the future without providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

We do not collect any unnecessary volume of information, or any unnecessary information, or any information that is unsuitable for achieving the purpose described above. However, the Information you have provided to us may be transferred to another party in connection with an acquisition of our company.

We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information we collect about you, except as described in this Privacy Policy. We never use or share personal information in ways unrelated to the ones described in this Privacy Policy, and we will not do so in the future without providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

We do not collect any unnecessary volume of information, or any unnecessary information, or any information that is unsuitable for achieving the purpose described above.

However, we may transfer the information you have provided to us if another party purchases all or a share of MailUp.

## (5) Email and Newsletter Policy

We comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act of 2003. We will not send you marketing messages if you have opted out. You can choose not to receive messages in the future by following the “unsubscribe” instructions located near the bottom of each email. We will not share, sell, rent, swap or authorize any third party to use your email address for commercial purposes without your permission. If you feel you have received an email from us in error, please contact **[support@beefree.io](mailto:support@beefree.io)** **.**

## (6) Security measures

We use security measures – such as storing your Information in an encrypted format and aggregate form – to avoid the misuse of such Information. In particular, we use Asymmetric Public Key Encryption RSA technology and our database is accessible only by authorized people with special access rights, who are required to keep the information confidential.

However, the safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping said password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

## (7) Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our Website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Website and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## (8) Credit card number and billing information

With regard to payment information for BEE Plugin and BEE Pro subscriptions, we use [Chargify](https://www.chargify.com/) as the recurring billing platform and [Chase Paymentech](https://merchantservices.chase.com/) as the payment gateway and merchant account provider. They are both Level 1 PCI Compliant providers, the highest level a business can attain. You can find more information about their privacy and security policies at **<https://www.chargify.com/privacy-policy/>** and **<https://www.chasepaymentech.com/privacypolicy/>**.

## (9) How we respond to Do Not Track signals

We may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioural tracking). Certain web browsers allow you to instruct your browser to send Do Not Track (“ **DNT** ”) signals to websites you visit, informing those sites that you do not want your online activities to be tracked. We do not currently respond to those signals. If you block cookies, certain features on our sites may not work. If you block or reject cookies, not all of the tracking described here will stop.

## (10) Accessing and correcting your Information

You can review and change your Information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page. You may also send us an e-mail at: **support@beefree.io** to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

In addition, if you are a resident of the EEA, you can object to processing of your Information, ask us to restrict processing of your Information or request portability of your Information. Again, you can exercise these rights by emailing us at **[support@beefree.io](mailto:support@beefree.io)**. We cannot delete your Information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change Information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect. You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your Information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority. Contact details for data protection authorities in the EEA are available [here](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm).

## (11) Legal Basis for Processing Personal Information (EEA Persons Only)

If you are from the European Economic Area, our legal basis for collecting and using the Information described above will depend on the Information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it.

However, we will normally collect and use Information from you where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data-protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. Typically, our legitimate interests include improving, maintaining, providing, and enhancing our technology, products, and services; ensuring the security of our services and our Websites; for our marketing activities; and to perform a contract with you. In some limited cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect Information from you. If we ask you to provide Information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contact with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your Information is mandatory or not, as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your Information.

Where required by law, we will collect Personal Information only where we have your consent to do so.

## (12) Retention of Data

We retain Information where we have an ongoing legitimate business or legal need to do so. Our retention periods will vary depending on the type of data involved, but, generally, we’ll refer to these criteria in order to determine retention period:

  * Whether we have a legal or contractual need to retain the data.
  * Whether the data is necessary to provide our Services.
  * Whether our clients have the ability to access and delete the data within their accounts.
  * Whether our client would reasonably expect that we would retain the data until they remove it or until their accounts are closed or terminated.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your Information, we will either delete or anonymize it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your Information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your Information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

## (13) Changes to our Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Privacy Policy on this page with a notice that the Privacy Policy has been updated on the Website home page.  If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you by posting a prominent notice on our Website indicating at the top of the Notice when it was most recently updated. The date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.

This policy was **last modified on July 31, 2018**. It was substantially modified to be compliant with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), a regulation in EU law on data protection and privacy for all individuals within the European Union (EU) and the European Economic Area (EEA). The GDPR also addresses the export of personal data outside the EU and EEA areas. Please read the new policy in its entirety.

## (14) Your consent

**BY USING OUR SITE, YOU ACCEPT OUR PRIVACY POLICY.**

## Contact Information

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices, you can contact MailUp, Inc. at **[support@beefree.io](mailto:support@beefree.io)** or by writing to the following address:

MailUp, Inc.  
c/o WeWork, 1111 Broadway,  
Suite 300,  
Oakland, CA 94607

Beefree uses cookies to offer you a better browsing experience. We use these for advertising and analytics purposes. By continuing to use the site, you agree to the use of cookies. Accept [Read More](https://beefree.io/cookies-policy/)
